# **Holly Leal**

hollyhleal@gmail.com | 860.501.1873 | Lakewood, CO

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/hollyleal/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/hollyleal/</a> | GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/hollyhleal/">https://github.com/hollyhleal/</a> |

Portfolio: https://hollyhleal.github.io/react-portfolio/

#### Summary

Full-stack web developer with four years of professional experience in project management for a digital agency & software provider. Spring 2023 graduate from the University of Denver coding boot camp with a certificate in full-stack web development. Enthusiastic and dedicated team player known for consistent communication and follow-through in a fast-paced environment.

#### **Skills**

Frontend: HTML5, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, JSON, ES6, Bootstrap, AJAX

**Backend**: MySQL, MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node, Handlebars, Sequelize, NoSQL **Full-Stack & Non-Technical**: Agile Methodology, Kanban, Git, Document Object Model, API Integrations, Object-Oriented Programming, Testing, ProWorkFlow, Jira, Progressive Web Apps, MERN Stack, Wireframes, Entity-Relationship Diagrams

## **Work Experience**

# MembersFirst | Project Manager

July 2019 - January 2023

Wayland, MA/Remote

- Hand-selected to manage the largest implementation the company has ever had, for 19 custom websites and 18 mobile apps
- Performed rigorous site review and testing prior to each site launch to ensure optimal appearance, completeness, and functional operation
- Spearheaded a time tracking initiative to evaluate and adjust pricing for each MembersFirst product offering

### MembersFirst | Project Associate

January 2019 - July 2019

Wayland, MA

- Assisted in all phases of website design and production (content loading, image optimization, semantic HTML structuring)
- Through an extensive QA process, ensured all new websites and website redesigns met WCAG 2.1AA standards for accessibility, best practices, and SEO guidelines

#### **Education**

University of Denver, Denver, CO

January 2023 - April 2023

Full-Stack Coding Boot Camp Certificate

University of Massachusetts Amherst, Amherst, MA

August 2013 - May 2017

Isenberg School of Management

Bachelor of Science in Hospitality and Tourism Management